cambridge.org 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy - Cambridge University Press

## About us 

This website is operated by Cambridge University Press, which is a Syndicate of the University of Cambridge. Our principal place of business is at the Edinburgh Building, Shaftesbury Road, Cambridge, CB2 8RU. Cambridge University Press, the University of Cambridge and its associated companies will use the information we collect from you in accordance with this policy. A list of our associated companies is available on request to [legalservices@cambridge.org](mailto:legalservices@cambridge.org). 

## Our approach 

Your privacy is important to us. We want to make sure that when we collect information from you we do so in a way that does not infringe your privacy. Our policy explains how we do this. 

**By registering or placing an order on this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.**

## Collection of information 

We may collect names, email and postal addresses, telephone numbers, professions, purchase and mailing history from you if you order from us or complete an online form (for instance to join our email services).

## Use of information

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to our website and to carry out administration, statistical analysis and market research. If you have requested any goods or services then we will use your information to supply the goods or services, to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning your order.

Where you have consented, we may contact you on occasion by post, telephone, fax and email about products and services we think might be of interest to you. If you decide in the future that do not want to receive such information, please email [mlist@cambridge.org](mailto:mlist@cambridge.org).

Where you have consented, we may make your details available to other reputable organisations whose product or services we think might be of interest to you. If you decide in the future that you do not want us to make your information available in this way please email [mlist@cambridge.org](mailto:mlist@cambridge.org).

We may transfer your personal details to other regions in which we have offices throughout the world, namely Europe, the Middle East and Africa; the Americas; and Asia-Pacific. You should be aware that some of our branches are in countries which do not have data protection laws. If you do not want us to make the information available in this way email [mlist@cambridge.org](mailto:mlist@cambridge.org).

We may disclose your information to our agents and service providers for the purposes set out above.

All personal information received by you is subject to processing centrally in the Europe branch of Cambridge University Press, England. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

## Cookies

We use cookies on this web site. Cookies are small amounts of information that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser. They tell us when you have visited our site and where you have been. They do not identify you personally, just the presence of your browser. Cookies make it easier for you to log on and use the site during future visits. They also enable us to provide you with a more personalised service. Should you wish to do so, your browser’s help section should be able to warn you before accepting cookies and how to filter or disable them, although in the latter case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site.

## Accessing and updating

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us at [legalservices@cambridge.org](mailto:legalservices@cambridge.org). We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

## Contact

If you have any requests in relation to the use we make of your information, please email [mlist@cambridge.org](mailto:mlist@cambridge.org). 

All other comments and queries relating to the administration of your relationship with us, our use of your information and this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to The Legal Services Director, Cambridge University Press, The Edinburgh Building, Shaftesbury Road, Cambridge, CB2 8RU, England ([legalservices@cambridge.org](mailto:legalservices@cambridge.org)).
